

# **EDUCATION**

## **BSC. COMPUTER SCIENCE**

**Anchor University** 

## **OND GEOLOGY**

University of Lagos

## **BSC. ANATOMY**

University of Benin

## **CERTIFICATION**

# **COURSERA CERTIFICATES**

- UI/UX Specialization
- Graphic Design & Design Principles
- Front-End Development

## **Phone**

- +234 81 2017 9204
- +234 90 3852 0113

#### **Email**

ojeriakhijeza@gmail.com jezaojeriakhi@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Oklar Royale Ave, Lagos, Nigeria.

Zip Code - 100234

#### **Portfolio**

jezastudio.github.io/portfolio

# **JEZA** OJERIAKHI

# GRAPHIC DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative Designer with over 8 years of experience working with growing businesses and individuals to achieve their goals. Confident in my ability to take on a both a designer and developer role, as well as collaborate with teams or individuals, to provide solutions to businesses needs.

#### **IMPORTANT SKILLS:**

- Graphic Design Illustrations
  - - Time Management

- Branding
- Motion Graphics
- Social Media Management - Teamwork & Collaboration
- UI/UX Design - Product Design - Front-End Dev.
  - Problem Solving
- Communication

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

## Oaks Communication Ltd/ Lagos Nigeria (2017-2018)

- Developing unique brand identities, logos, and comprehensive brand guidelines.
- Developing innovative ad creatives for various digital channels.
- Incorporating feedback and revisions to refine designs and achieve client satisfaction.

## VISUAL DESIGNER

# Parachute Design Group/Toronto Canada (2018-2020)

- From creating graphic designs & motion graphics to creating brand identities and social media management.
- Designing and implementing creative UI/UX solutions.
- Creating compelling pitch decks.
- Managing multiple projects and meeting deadlines.

#### **CREATIVE DESIGNER / ART DIRECTOR**

## Explicit Communication/Lagos Nigeria (2020-2023)

- Working with a team of talented creatives and a marketing team in creating designs, handling content creation and coming up with intuitive brand marketing strategies.
- Developing and maintaining responsive web interfaces using HTML, CSS and JavaScript

## SOFTWARE SKILL

Adobe photoshop	Microsoft Office Tools	Adobe inDesign
Adobe Illustrator	CorelDraw	Adobe XD
Figma	HTML-S/CSS-3	
Adobe Animate	WordPress	